<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dairy-Free on Passionfruit Kitchen</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/tags/dairy-free/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dairy-Free on Passionfruit Kitchen</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 19:40:58 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/tags/dairy-free/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Microwave Steamed Eggs</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/microwave-steamed-eggs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 19:40:58 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/microwave-steamed-eggs/</guid>
      <description>Steamed eggs, or what I called 炖蛋 growing up, has always been one of my comfort foods. My grandma used to make it for me when I was sick, and it was one of the first things I learned how to cook. It&amp;rsquo;s also so simple &amp;ndash; it&amp;rsquo;s just a savory, super simple steamed egg dish. It&amp;rsquo;s technically an egg custard, but that sounds scary, and this isn&amp;rsquo;t complicated or scary at all. If you&amp;rsquo;ve ever heard of the Japanese dish chawanmushi or the Korean dish gyeran-jjim, this is in a similar vein. It&amp;rsquo;s lowkey, homey, and comforting, and as a bonus you&amp;rsquo;re practically guaranteed to have the ingredients you need to make it at home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sunshine Smoothie Bowl</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/sunshine-smoothie-bowl/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 11:11:14 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/sunshine-smoothie-bowl/</guid>
      <description>Wow, I&amp;rsquo;m excited about this one! It&amp;rsquo;s so simple yet so good - I think I&amp;rsquo;ve made it like six times this month already. I call it a sunshine smoothie bowl because of the color, but to be more specific it&amp;rsquo;s an amazing tropical smoothie bowl - mango, pineapple, banana (and anything else you might want to add!) I&amp;rsquo;ve got a neat trick as well for making sure it&amp;rsquo;s thick enough to scoop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegetarian Gua Bao</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/vegetarian-gua-bao/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 20:24:47 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/vegetarian-gua-bao/</guid>
      <description>Gua bao is a dish I grew up with! Basically, it&amp;rsquo;s often eaten as a split bun stuffed with pork belly and cucumber and sometimes other toppings like cilantro. Although as a child, my strongest memory is taking those split buns and making them into odd fusion PB&amp;amp;J sandwiches! After I went pescetarian, I missed having gua bao, so I came up with a vegetarian substitute that swaps mushrooms for pork belly. It tastes just as good!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rice Paper Sushi</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/rice-paper-roll/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 20:24:47 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/rice-paper-roll/</guid>
      <description>My family sometimes likes to make sushi at home. Granted, it&amp;rsquo;s probably not very authentic, but it still tastes pretty good. We usually make it with surimi, cucumber, and avocado; sometimes we swap surimi for smoked salmon. So, how did this recipe come about? A few weeks ago I was grocery shopping and bought some rice paper, mostly because I&amp;rsquo;ve seen it being used a ton of ways on Instagram and wanted to give it a try. When my family was making sushi together later that weekend, I looked at the rice paper and came up with a neat idea &amp;ndash; why not use it in sushi?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Valentines Day Dango</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/dango/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 20:24:47 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/dango/</guid>
      <description>Happy Valentines Day! In honor of the holiday, I figured I should take advantage of that bottle of pink food coloring in my baking cabinet (fun fact, it’s the only color I have!) This is inspired by hanami dango, which is one of the cutest desserts I’ve ever had. I love dango because they are so simple, not to sweet, and so chewy. Traditionally hanami dango are pink, white, and green, but I made it with just pink and white for Valentines Day!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slow Cooker Applesauce</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/slow-cooker-applesauce/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 20:24:47 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/slow-cooker-applesauce/</guid>
      <description>I had wayyy too many apples in the fridge. Like, maybe 15? Some of them were getting far too old, and it was time to use them up. Usually with apples, I would make apple crisp or apple pie, but with robotics season starting I didn&amp;rsquo;t have time. So my solution? Slow cooker applesauce! It&amp;rsquo;s great because you can set it and forget it until it&amp;rsquo;s ready, it tastes great, and it makes the house smell so cozy, which is just what you need in these winter months. (Now the only question is squeezing 10 apples into my slow cooker&amp;hellip;)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quick Roasted Broccoli</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/quick-roasted-broccoli/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 22:55:04 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/quick-roasted-broccoli/</guid>
      <description>Roasted broccoli is simple, healthy, and versatile. It’s a quick recipe, easy to customize, and surprisingly addictive. I made a batch of roasted broccoli a few days ago, and my family snacked on it before dinner until half of it was gone!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 Ingredient Peanut Butter Blossoms</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/5-ingredient-peanut-butter-blossoms/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 20:08:33 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/5-ingredient-peanut-butter-blossoms/</guid>
      <description>Peanut butter cookies are usually a big disappointment for me. Peanut butter cookies tend to bake up very dry because of the way that the peanut butter affects the cookie texture. And that&amp;rsquo;s a huge shame, because peanut butter is so delicious on its own!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Red Curry Fried Rice</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/red-curry-fried-rice/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 17:46:35 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/red-curry-fried-rice/</guid>
      <description>Fried rice is one of my favorite meals to make. It’s the perfect clean-out-the-fridge dinner, and it’s quick and so easy to cook. Growing up, my grandparents would make egg fried rice with leftover pork or even ham and frozen mixed vegetables.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shrimp &amp; Egg Stir Fry</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/shrimp-egg-stir-fry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 20:25:04 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/shrimp-egg-stir-fry/</guid>
      <description>When I was young, we used to get takeout from this one place in Chinatown (I don’t know the name, sadly.) I specifically remember this one dish I loved: their stir-fried shrimp and eggs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garlic Chive &amp; Egg Stir Fry</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/garlic-chive-egg-stir-fry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 20:24:15 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/garlic-chive-egg-stir-fry/</guid>
      <description>Unlike chives, which you’d normally think of as an aromatic, garlic chives are treated like a vegetable and used in stir-fries, dumpling fillings, and more. My favorite way to cook them is very simple, just quickly stir-fried with some scrambled eggs. The chives bring a refreshing, delicious flavor to the dish, and it’s absolutely delicious! It’s also so quick to whip up for dinner on a busy day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Red Curry Noodle Soup</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/red-curry-noodle-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 22:54:49 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/red-curry-noodle-soup/</guid>
      <description>Creamy, spicy, savory, coconutty…this soup is possibly one of the best things I’ve ever made. My family definitely agrees – whenever I make this, it’s gone in a day! It’s a great comfort food for winter and also great to make in the summer, since I always crave spicy food in the summer. I love this soup so much!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ube Mooncakes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/ube-mooncakes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 20:24:28 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/ube-mooncakes/</guid>
      <description>Mooncakes are a symbolic dessert traditionally eaten on the Mid Autumn Festival. They are decorated with elaborate stamped designs and characters on top. Mooncakes are traditionally baked pastries with a rich filling. The pastry layer is akin to a soft cookie, while the filling can be savory or sweet. Traditional fillings include lotus seed paste with salted egg yolk, red bean paste, mixed nutes, and jujube or date paste.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brown Rice &#39;Jambalaya&#39; (Instant Pot Recipe!)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/jambalaya/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 20:24:06 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/jambalaya/</guid>
      <description>I love jambalaya. It’s traditionally not pescetarian, so I swapped chicken for mushrooms and used vegetarian sausage to make my version. I also used brown rice instead of white rice, since that’s my family’s favorite type of rice. It also adds body to the jambalaya, so I prefer using it, even though it isn’t traditional. Since I don’t usually have the patience to cook the rice on a stovetop, I used my instant pot instead to make it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ratatouille Shakshuka</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/ratatouille-shakshuka/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 20:24:55 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/ratatouille-shakshuka/</guid>
      <description>I know this probably sounds weird, but ratatouille + shakshuka is a surprisingly good combo. If you’ve never heard of ratatouille before, it’s a French Provencal vegetable stew typically made with the freshest of summer produce – zucchini, tomatoes, eggplant. Shakshuka is a dish of eggs poached in tomato sauce, which has many variations that can be found around the Mediterranean and Northern Africa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Honey Soy Salmon</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/honey-soy-salmon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 20:19:22 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/honey-soy-salmon/</guid>
      <description>Salmon is a popular and easy dinner to make. A common way to make it is roasting it in the oven, which I used to do all the time. Except the problem is, I kept ending up with overcooked salmon, because the oven was too hot. And using the oven is such as hassle – you have to preheat it, and defrost the salmon, and what not.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Easy Shrimp Cocktail (2 ways!)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/easy-shrimp-cocktail/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 21:12:02 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/easy-shrimp-cocktail/</guid>
      <description>I know you can buy the elements at the store, but I prefer to make this shrimp cocktail from scratch. It’s only a few ingredients and takes barely any time at all. Plus, it’s better made fresh. For a spin on the classic, I replaced the typical super-sweet ketchup with a homemade tomato sauce that’s tomatoey, spicy, just the right amount of sweet, and absolutely delish. I also made another version with a mango chili dipping sauce, which is an awesome combination with the shrimp!</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
