<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Desserts on Passionfruit Kitchen</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/categories/desserts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Desserts on Passionfruit Kitchen</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 20:24:47 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/categories/desserts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Valentines Day Dango</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/dango/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 20:24:47 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/dango/</guid>
      <description>Happy Valentines Day! In honor of the holiday, I figured I should take advantage of that bottle of pink food coloring in my baking cabinet (fun fact, it’s the only color I have!) This is inspired by hanami dango, which is one of the cutest desserts I’ve ever had. I love dango because they are so simple, not to sweet, and so chewy. Traditionally hanami dango are pink, white, and green, but I made it with just pink and white for Valentines Day!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slow Cooker Applesauce</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/slow-cooker-applesauce/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 20:24:47 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/slow-cooker-applesauce/</guid>
      <description>I had wayyy too many apples in the fridge. Like, maybe 15? Some of them were getting far too old, and it was time to use them up. Usually with apples, I would make apple crisp or apple pie, but with robotics season starting I didn&amp;rsquo;t have time. So my solution? Slow cooker applesauce! It&amp;rsquo;s great because you can set it and forget it until it&amp;rsquo;s ready, it tastes great, and it makes the house smell so cozy, which is just what you need in these winter months. (Now the only question is squeezing 10 apples into my slow cooker&amp;hellip;)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chewy Brown Butter Mochi</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/chewy-butter-mochi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 20:07:55 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/chewy-butter-mochi/</guid>
      <description>Butter mochi is becoming popular these days. It originates from Hawaii, and fuses traditional Japanese mochi with Western ingredients. Unlike Japanese mochi, it&amp;rsquo;s baked, and can be cut into bars. This gives it a different texture &amp;ndash; a little bit crispy, and more fluffy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Best Cheesecake Bars</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/cheesecake-bars/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 20:08:01 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/cheesecake-bars/</guid>
      <description>While round cheesecakes are impressive when you do get them right, I prefer to hedge my bets by making cheesecake bars. I prefer their taste over regular cheesecake because they have a higher crust to filling ratio, so they&amp;rsquo;re more balanced. And they are much easier to make!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 Ingredient Peanut Butter Blossoms</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/5-ingredient-peanut-butter-blossoms/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 20:08:33 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/5-ingredient-peanut-butter-blossoms/</guid>
      <description>Peanut butter cookies are usually a big disappointment for me. Peanut butter cookies tend to bake up very dry because of the way that the peanut butter affects the cookie texture. And that&amp;rsquo;s a huge shame, because peanut butter is so delicious on its own!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Banana Coffee Cake</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/banana-coffee-cake/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 20:07:42 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/banana-coffee-cake/</guid>
      <description>Banana bread is a classic bake, and it definitely got more popular during lockdown! My dad makes an awesome banana bread that I&amp;rsquo;ll always love, but I was looking for a moister banana bread. I combined this banana bread recipe with a recipe for coffee cake (because who doesn&amp;rsquo;t love streusel?) and the combination was stellar!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ube Mooncakes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/ube-mooncakes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 20:24:28 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/ube-mooncakes/</guid>
      <description>Mooncakes are a symbolic dessert traditionally eaten on the Mid Autumn Festival. They are decorated with elaborate stamped designs and characters on top. Mooncakes are traditionally baked pastries with a rich filling. The pastry layer is akin to a soft cookie, while the filling can be savory or sweet. Traditional fillings include lotus seed paste with salted egg yolk, red bean paste, mixed nutes, and jujube or date paste.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Set Up a Cheeseboard</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/how-to-set-up-a-cheeseboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 20:07:11 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/how-to-set-up-a-cheeseboard/</guid>
      <description>A big cheeseboard is also the perfect appetizer at a holdiay party! I always used to see all these photos of fancy cheeseboards on Instagram and Pinterest, and I’d wish I could make something similar. There are a few steps to making a cheeseboard, which I cover in this guide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oatmeal Muffins (5 ways!)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/oatmeal-muffins-5-ways/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 20:24:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/oatmeal-muffins-5-ways/</guid>
      <description>A lot of muffins I find in stores are very sweet and very dry, so I prefer to make my own. Homemade muffins are the best, especially warm out of the oven. They only need a bowl and a whisk, and they’re so easy to customize! My recipe has no refined sugar and has oats for added fiber and texture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 Spice Pumpkin Pie</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/5-spice-pumpkin-pie/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 20:24:40 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/5-spice-pumpkin-pie/</guid>
      <description>Pumpkin pie was one of the first things I ever learned how to bake! I originally used the Libby’s pumpkin pie recipe, but after a while, I got sick of baking the same recipe again and again. So I started to tinker with the recipe (to the delight of my family, of course) and I came up with the idea of using Chinese five spice instead of pumpkin pie spice. It gives the pie so much more depth of flavor.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
