<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Soups &amp; Stews on Passionfruit Kitchen</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/featured_categories/soups--stews/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Soups &amp; Stews on Passionfruit Kitchen</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 19:40:58 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/featured_categories/soups--stews/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Microwave Steamed Eggs</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/microwave-steamed-eggs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 19:40:58 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/microwave-steamed-eggs/</guid>
      <description>Steamed eggs, or what I called 炖蛋 growing up, has always been one of my comfort foods. My grandma used to make it for me when I was sick, and it was one of the first things I learned how to cook. It&amp;rsquo;s also so simple &amp;ndash; it&amp;rsquo;s just a savory, super simple steamed egg dish. It&amp;rsquo;s technically an egg custard, but that sounds scary, and this isn&amp;rsquo;t complicated or scary at all. If you&amp;rsquo;ve ever heard of the Japanese dish chawanmushi or the Korean dish gyeran-jjim, this is in a similar vein. It&amp;rsquo;s lowkey, homey, and comforting, and as a bonus you&amp;rsquo;re practically guaranteed to have the ingredients you need to make it at home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baked Brie Pastries</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/baked-brie/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 13:39:35 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/baked-brie/</guid>
      <description>This is a festive dish that looks fancy, tastes amazing, and is actually very simple to make! It&amp;rsquo;s a riff on Baked Brie, which is a common holiday appetizer, but reimagined to be in individual pastry form. It makes a great appetizer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cheesy Shells</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/cheesy-shells/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 16:12:43 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/cheesy-shells/</guid>
      <description>This is a pretty awesome mac and cheese recipe. It&amp;rsquo;s got tons of flavor, and it uses shell pasta instead of elbow macaroni because shells are the superior shape (I will die on this hill). It&amp;rsquo;s extra saucy, because the saucier the better. It&amp;rsquo;s salty, cheesy, and has a bit of a kick; peak comfort food right here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Red Curry Noodle Soup</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/red-curry-noodle-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 22:54:49 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/red-curry-noodle-soup/</guid>
      <description>Creamy, spicy, savory, coconutty…this soup is possibly one of the best things I’ve ever made. My family definitely agrees – whenever I make this, it’s gone in a day! It’s a great comfort food for winter and also great to make in the summer, since I always crave spicy food in the summer. I love this soup so much!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brown Rice &#39;Jambalaya&#39; (Instant Pot Recipe!)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/jambalaya/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 20:24:06 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/jambalaya/</guid>
      <description>I love jambalaya. It’s traditionally not pescetarian, so I swapped chicken for mushrooms and used vegetarian sausage to make my version. I also used brown rice instead of white rice, since that’s my family’s favorite type of rice. It also adds body to the jambalaya, so I prefer using it, even though it isn’t traditional. Since I don’t usually have the patience to cook the rice on a stovetop, I used my instant pot instead to make it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broccoli Cheddar Soup</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/broccoli-cheddar-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 22:53:59 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/broccoli-cheddar-soup/</guid>
      <description>Who else loves broccoli cheddar soup? I adored it as a kid, and for me, the quintessential benchmark was Panera Bread&amp;rsquo;s rendition &amp;ndash; comfort in a bread bowl. Unfortunately, I’ve had also quite a few bad broccoli cheddar soups in my life (school cafeteria, anyone?) — floury, bland, watery, and sometimes the broccoli inside would still be crunchy (yikes). But, in pursuit of the Panera Bread dreams of my childhood, I took to experimenting with making it at home.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
