<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Desserts on Passionfruit Kitchen</title>
    <link>https://kchenturtles.github.io/PassionfruitKitchen/en/featured_categories/desserts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Desserts on Passionfruit Kitchen</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 20:24:28 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://kchenturtles.github.io/PassionfruitKitchen/en/featured_categories/desserts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ube Mooncakes</title>
      <link>https://kchenturtles.github.io/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/ube-mooncakes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 20:24:28 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kchenturtles.github.io/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/ube-mooncakes/</guid>
      <description>Mooncakes are a symbolic dessert traditionally eaten on the Mid Autumn Festival. They are decorated with elaborate stamped designs and characters on top. Mooncakes are traditionally baked pastries with a rich filling. The pastry layer is akin to a soft cookie, while the filling can be savory or sweet. Traditional fillings include lotus seed paste with salted egg yolk, red bean paste, mixed nutes, and jujube or date paste.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Set Up a Cheeseboard</title>
      <link>https://kchenturtles.github.io/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/how-to-set-up-a-cheeseboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 20:07:11 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kchenturtles.github.io/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/how-to-set-up-a-cheeseboard/</guid>
      <description>A big cheeseboard is also the perfect appetizer at a holdiay party! I always used to see all these photos of fancy cheeseboards on Instagram and Pinterest, and I’d wish I could make something similar. There are a few steps to making a cheeseboard, which I cover in this guide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oatmeal Muffins (5 ways!)</title>
      <link>https://kchenturtles.github.io/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/oatmeal-muffins-5-ways/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 20:24:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kchenturtles.github.io/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/oatmeal-muffins-5-ways/</guid>
      <description>A lot of muffins I find in stores are very sweet and very dry, so I prefer to make my own. Homemade muffins are the best, especially warm out of the oven. They only need a bowl and a whisk, and they’re so easy to customize! My recipe has no refined sugar and has oats for added fiber and texture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 Spice Pumpkin Pie</title>
      <link>https://kchenturtles.github.io/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/5-spice-pumpkin-pie/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 20:24:40 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kchenturtles.github.io/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/5-spice-pumpkin-pie/</guid>
      <description>Pumpkin pie was one of the first things I ever learned how to bake! I originally used the Libby’s pumpkin pie recipe, but after a while, I got sick of baking the same recipe again and again. So I started to tinker with the recipe (to the delight of my family, of course) and I came up with the idea of using Chinese five spice instead of pumpkin pie spice. It gives the pie so much more depth of flavor.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
