<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pescetarian on Passionfruit Kitchen</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/tags/pescetarian/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pescetarian on Passionfruit Kitchen</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 00:35:51 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/tags/pescetarian/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Breakfast Strata</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/breakfast-strata/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 00:35:51 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/breakfast-strata/</guid>
      <description>This might be the best thing I&amp;rsquo;ve ever made. And that&amp;rsquo;s saying a lot. But everyone who tried this thinks the same thing, so&amp;hellip;yeah, it&amp;rsquo;s pretty tasty. Strata is a bit like a savory bread pudding, or stale bread baked in custard, and this take is pretty great!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pigs in a Blanket</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/pigs-in-a-blanket/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 00:24:55 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/pigs-in-a-blanket/</guid>
      <description>Wow, it&amp;rsquo;s been busy recently! I&amp;rsquo;ve been sticking to the simple recipes to get by: just a couple of ingredients, not too many dishes dirtied, less prep work. Luckily for me, these vegetarian pigs in a blanket check all of those boxes, and they taste great!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Savory Crepe, Jian Bing Style</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/jianbing-crepe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 20:24:47 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/jianbing-crepe/</guid>
      <description>My dad&amp;rsquo;s favorite food is probably jian bing, a Chinese street food that usually consists of a crispy whole-wheat crepe filled with egg, black bean sauce, scallions, sometimes lettuce, and a crispy cracker or fried dough piece. As a little bit of fun, this Father&amp;rsquo;s Day I made a version using French crepe batter, which produces a smoother and softer crepe than the traditional Chinese Version. I don&amp;rsquo;t have the plate that vendors typically use to make jian bing, but I made do with what I had. This dish is essentially my recreation of a jian bing, just a little bit simpler and quicker to make!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegetarian Gua Bao</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/vegetarian-gua-bao/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 20:24:47 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/vegetarian-gua-bao/</guid>
      <description>Gua bao is a dish I grew up with! Basically, it&amp;rsquo;s often eaten as a split bun stuffed with pork belly and cucumber and sometimes other toppings like cilantro. Although as a child, my strongest memory is taking those split buns and making them into odd fusion PB&amp;amp;J sandwiches! After I went pescetarian, I missed having gua bao, so I came up with a vegetarian substitute that swaps mushrooms for pork belly. It tastes just as good!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crispy Rice Paper Wrap</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/rice-paper-egg-wrap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 20:24:47 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/rice-paper-egg-wrap/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m back with the rice paper, because I&amp;rsquo;ve still got some left! Rice paper is also really good for crisping up, and it makes a really cool substitute for a tortilla in a breakfast egg wrap. This recipe is somewhat inspired by the Chinese dish jian bing, which has eggs and scallions on top of a crepe with black bean sauce. I tried out swapping the tortilla with rice paper, and it turned out great!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rice Paper Sushi Rolls</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/rice-paper-roll/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 20:24:47 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/rice-paper-roll/</guid>
      <description>My family likes to make sushi at home. Granted, it&amp;rsquo;s probably not very authentic, but it still tastes great! We usually make it with surimi, cucumber, and avocado, sometimes we swap surimi for smoked salmon. So, how did this recipe come about? Well, a few weeks ago I was grocery shopping and bought some rice paper, mostly because I&amp;rsquo;ve seen it being used a ton of ways on Instagram and wanted to give it a try. When my family was making sushi together later that weekend, I looked at the rice paper and came up with a neat idea &amp;ndash; why not wrap sushi in it?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Valentines Day Dango</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/dango/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 20:24:47 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/dango/</guid>
      <description>Happy Valentines Day! In honor of the holiday, I figured I should take advantage of that bottle of pink food coloring in my baking cabinet (fun fact, it’s the only color I have!) This is inspired by hanami dango, which is one of the cutest desserts I’ve ever had. I love dango because they are so simple, not to sweet, and so chewy. Traditionally hanami dango are pink, white, and green, but I made it with just pink and white for Valentines Day!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slow Cooker Applesauce</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/slow-cooker-applesauce/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 20:24:47 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/slow-cooker-applesauce/</guid>
      <description>I had wayyy too many apples in the fridge. Like, maybe 15? Some of them were getting far too old, and it was time to use them up. Usually with apples, I would make apple crisp or apple pie, but with robotics season starting I didn&amp;rsquo;t have time. So my solution? Slow cooker applesauce! It&amp;rsquo;s great because you can set it and forget it until it&amp;rsquo;s ready, it tastes great, and it makes the house smell so cozy, which is just what you need in these winter months. (Now the only question is squeezing 10 apples into my slow cooker&amp;hellip;)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Egg Toast</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/korean-egg-toast/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 20:24:47 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/korean-egg-toast/</guid>
      <description>This winter, I got introduced to Korean egg toast, and I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure I&amp;rsquo;ve had it like every day this week. It&amp;rsquo;s so good &amp;ndash; the softest, fluffiest egg ever, folded into sweet brioche bread and topped with the perfect sweet-and-savory sauce. My favorite toast also has cheese and avocado! Of course I had to try to figure out how to make it at home, so here is what I came up with!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four-Cheese Cheesy Shells</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/cheesy-shells/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 16:12:43 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/cheesy-shells/</guid>
      <description>This is a pretty awesome mac and cheese recipe. It&amp;rsquo;s got tons of flavor, and it uses shell pasta instead of elbow macaroni because shells are the superior shape (I will die on this hill). It&amp;rsquo;s extra saucy, because the saucier the better. It&amp;rsquo;s salty, cheesy, and has a bit of a kick (adjustable levels!) Peak comfort food right here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Best Cheesecake Bars</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/cheesecake-bars/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 20:08:01 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/cheesecake-bars/</guid>
      <description>While round cheesecakes are impressive when you do get them right, I prefer to hedge my bets by making cheesecake bars. I prefer their taste over regular cheesecake because they have a higher crust to filling ratio, so they&amp;rsquo;re more balanced. And they are much easier to make!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Peach Burrata Caprese Salad</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/peach-burrata-caprese-salad/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 21:11:39 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/peach-burrata-caprese-salad/</guid>
      <description>I conquered my fear of salads with this peach and burrata caprese. I made it for my parents’ anniversary dinner, and they loved it. Since it’s peach season, I threw in peaches with the classic tomato and basil caprese salad. I also replaced the traditional mozzarella with burrata, because I think it makes the salad more cohesive. It’s a super simple salad, dressed with just a drizzle of good balsamic vinegar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shrimp &amp; Egg Stir Fry</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/shrimp-egg-stir-fry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 20:25:04 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/shrimp-egg-stir-fry/</guid>
      <description>When I was young, we used to get takeout from this one place in Chinatown (I don’t know the name, sadly.) I specifically remember this one dish I loved: their stir-fried shrimp and eggs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garlic Chive &amp; Egg Stir Fry</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/garlic-chive-egg-stir-fry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 20:24:15 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/garlic-chive-egg-stir-fry/</guid>
      <description>Unlike chives, which you’d normally think of as an aromatic, garlic chives are treated like a vegetable and used in stir-fries, dumpling fillings, and more. My favorite way to cook them is very simple, just quickly stir-fried with some scrambled eggs. The chives bring a refreshing, delicious flavor to the dish, and it’s absolutely delicious! It’s also so quick to whip up for dinner on a busy day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ube Mooncakes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/ube-mooncakes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 20:24:28 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/ube-mooncakes/</guid>
      <description>Mooncakes are a symbolic dessert traditionally eaten on the Mid Autumn Festival. They are decorated with elaborate stamped designs and characters on top. Mooncakes are traditionally baked pastries with a rich filling. The pastry layer is akin to a soft cookie, while the filling can be savory or sweet. Traditional fillings include lotus seed paste with salted egg yolk, red bean paste, mixed nutes, and jujube or date paste.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brown Rice &#39;Jambalaya&#39; (Instant Pot Recipe!)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/jambalaya/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 20:24:06 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/jambalaya/</guid>
      <description>I love jambalaya. It’s traditionally not pescetarian, so I swapped chicken for mushrooms and used vegetarian sausage to make my version. I also used brown rice instead of white rice, since that’s my family’s favorite type of rice. It also adds body to the jambalaya, so I prefer using it, even though it isn’t traditional. Since I don’t usually have the patience to cook the rice on a stovetop, I used my instant pot instead to make it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Set Up a Cheeseboard</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/how-to-set-up-a-cheeseboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 20:07:11 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/how-to-set-up-a-cheeseboard/</guid>
      <description>A big cheeseboard is also the perfect appetizer at a holdiay party! I always used to see all these photos of fancy cheeseboards on Instagram and Pinterest, and I’d wish I could make something similar. There are a few steps to making a cheeseboard, which I cover in this guide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creamy Tomato Penne</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/creamy-tomato-penne/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 20:24:47 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/creamy-tomato-penne/</guid>
      <description>I love pasta alla vodka, but it does require two pots – one to boil the water, and one to mix the sauce. I was craving a good tomatoey pasta the other night, and I happened to have the idea to try a one-pot version, where the pasta cooks in the sauce (please don’t come for me, Italians.) The pasta turned out delicious, and it was so easy to make that I knew I had to put it in a recipe!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ratatouille Shakshuka</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/ratatouille-shakshuka/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 20:24:55 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/ratatouille-shakshuka/</guid>
      <description>I know this probably sounds weird, but ratatouille + shakshuka is a surprisingly good combo. If you’ve never heard of ratatouille before, it’s a French Provencal vegetable stew typically made with the freshest of summer produce – zucchini, tomatoes, eggplant. Shakshuka is a dish of eggs poached in tomato sauce, which has many variations that can be found around the Mediterranean and Northern Africa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Honey Soy Salmon</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/honey-soy-salmon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 20:19:22 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/honey-soy-salmon/</guid>
      <description>Salmon is a popular and easy dinner to make. A common way to make it is roasting it in the oven, which I used to do all the time. Except the problem is, I kept ending up with overcooked salmon, because the oven was too hot. And using the oven is such as hassle – you have to preheat it, and defrost the salmon, and what not.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caramelized Onion, Mushroom, &amp; Goat Cheese Tart</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/caramelized-onion-mushroom-goat-cheese-galette/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 20:24:22 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/caramelized-onion-mushroom-goat-cheese-galette/</guid>
      <description>I love caramelized onions. And mushrooms. And goat cheese. So I thought, why not put them all on top of a puff pastry base? It’s the perfect mix of sweet, savory caramelized onions and tangy, creamy goat cheese.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 Spice Pumpkin Pie</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/5-spice-pumpkin-pie/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 20:24:40 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/5-spice-pumpkin-pie/</guid>
      <description>Pumpkin pie was one of the first things I ever learned how to bake! I originally used the Libby’s pumpkin pie recipe, but after a while, I got sick of baking the same recipe again and again. So I started to tinker with the recipe (to the delight of my family, of course) and I came up with the idea of using Chinese five spice instead of pumpkin pie spice. It gives the pie so much more depth of flavor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Easy Shrimp Cocktail (2 ways!)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/easy-shrimp-cocktail/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 21:12:02 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/easy-shrimp-cocktail/</guid>
      <description>I know you can buy the elements at the store, but I prefer to make this shrimp cocktail from scratch. It’s only a few ingredients and takes barely any time at all. Plus, it’s better made fresh. For a spin on the classic, I replaced the typical super-sweet ketchup with a homemade tomato sauce that’s tomatoey, spicy, just the right amount of sweet, and absolutely delish. I also made another version with a mango chili dipping sauce, which is an awesome combination with the shrimp!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sesame Honey Cauliflower Wings</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/sesame-honey-cauliflower-wings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 21:04:12 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/PassionfruitKitchen/en/posts/sesame-honey-cauliflower-wings/</guid>
      <description>Cauliflower wings are an awesome vegetarian snack! I first made cauliflower wings when I made vegetarian buffalo wings for the Super Bowl, but I don’t love buffalo sauce, so I came up with a sesame-honey version instead. The sauce is sticky, sweet, and garlicky, and the cauliflower wings are deliciously crunchy.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
